What do you think?
ماذا تعتقد؟
This distraction method is not bad, right?
هذه الطريقة في التشتيت ليست سيئة، أليس كذلك؟
It's not bad.
إنه ليس سيئا.
But are you sure you can win the bid?
ولكن هل أنت متأكد من أنك تستطيع الفوز بالمناقصة؟
Of course.
بالطبع.
It's rare for me to be so serious.
من النادر بالنسبة لي أن أكون جادًا إلى هذا الحد.
We have to win the bid for sure.
علينا أن نفوز بالعطاء بالتأكيد.
Otherwise, how can I face Jiang Shaopeng?
وإلا فكيف أستطيع مواجهة جيانغ شاو بينغ؟
What has it got to do with Jiang Shaopeng?
ما علاقة هذا الأمر بجيانج شاو بنج؟
It's a secret. It won't be a secret if I tell you about it.
إنه سر، ولن يصبح سرًا إذا أخبرتك به.
♪Every breath is my♪
♪كل نفس لي♪
♪Honest narration♪
♪رواية صادقة♪
♪Love doesn't have to be spoken out loud♪
♪الحب لا يجب أن يُقال بصوت عالٍ♪
=See Your Love=
=انظر حبك=
=Episode 10=
=الحلقة العاشرة=
You entrusted me with it, Mr. Yang.
لقد أوكلت إليّ هذه المهمة، السيد يانغ.
Of course I'll get it done perfectly.
بالطبع سأنجزه على أكمل وجه.
Why did I receive news that the bids had been placed?
لماذا تلقيت خبر تقديم العطاءات؟
That's impossible.
هذا مستحيل.
Mr. Yang, I...
السيد. التي، أنا...
So, you were just pretending that you didn't want Hengfeng.
إذن، كنت تتظاهر فقط بأنك لا تريد هينغفينج.
Sean.
شون.
(Message)
(رسالة)
(Jessica: Your brother has cheated on me.)
(جيسيكا: لقد خدعني أخوك.)
After a series of tests,
بعد سلسلة من الاختبارات،
he's fine now.
إنه بخير الآن.
You don't have to worry.
لا داعي للقلق.
(Why are you here?)
(لماذا انت هنا؟)
He got into an accident. He's in room 602 now.
لقد تعرض لحادث وهو الآن في الغرفة 602.
Why are you worried about him?
لماذا أنت قلق عليه؟
What's your relationship with him?
ما هي علاقتك به؟
(We are friends.)
(نحن أصدقاء.)
Are you sure?
هل أنت متأكد؟
(He has a fiancee.)
(عنده خطيبة)
That was arranged by the chairman.
وقد تم ترتيب ذلك من قبل الرئيس.
He doesn't have a choice in his life or his relationship.
ليس لديه خيار في حياته أو علاقته.
Don't you know that?
ألا تعلم ذلك؟
(Even when it comes to my relationship,)
(حتى عندما يتعلق الأمر بعلاقتي)
(I can just resist passively.)
(أستطيع فقط أن أقاوم بشكل سلبي.)
He is so pitiful.
إنه مثير للشفقة للغاية.
In order to protect you,
من أجل حمايتك،
he let you quit your job in advance so that you could leave.
لقد سمح لك بترك وظيفتك مسبقًا حتى تتمكن من المغادرة.
He likes you. He wants to be with you.
إنه يحبك ويريد أن يكون معك.
He doesn't want you to think that he's useless.
إنه لا يريدك أن تظن أنه عديم الفائدة.
He works hard to prove himself.
إنه يعمل بجد لإثبات نفسه.
He is ready to go back and lay it out to the chairman.
وهو مستعد للعودة وعرض الأمر على الرئيس.
He's a fool.
إنه أحمق.
It's obvious that it won't go his way.
ومن الواضح أن الأمر لن يسير وفق ما يريد.
And you
وأنت
just treat him as a friend.
فقط تعامل معه كصديق.
♪You are the only one who can protect me♪
♪أنت الوحيد الذي يستطيع حمايتي♪
♪We can decide on our own touching story♪
♪يمكننا أن نقرر قصتنا المؤثرة بأنفسنا♪
♪Nothing can replace this soundless love♪
لا شيء يمكن أن يحل محل هذا الحب الصامت
♪I stop talking when I see you running away from me every day♪
♪أتوقف عن الحديث عندما أراك تهرب مني كل يوم♪
(The language that belongs to only you.)
(اللغة التي تنتمي إليك فقط.)
♪I look for you from the sea of people♪
♪أبحث عنك من بين بحر الناس♪
♪I want to say I love you♪
♪أريد أن أقول أنني أحبك♪
(I like you.)
(أنا معجب بك.)
♪I can only wait like a fool because I can't hear anything♪
♪لا أستطيع إلا الانتظار مثل الأحمق لأنني لا أستطيع سماع أي شيء♪
♪Both hearts are holding onto each other♪
♪ كلا القلبين يتمسكان ببعضهما البعض♪
♪I want to stop, I want to give up♪
♪أريد أن أتوقف، أريد أن أستسلم♪
♪I want to forget how much pain I've been through♪
♪أريد أن أنسى مقدار الألم الذي مررت به♪
♪I can't escape from the memory♪
♪لا أستطيع الهروب من الذاكرة♪
♪Where I can see I'm being loved♪
♪حيث أستطيع أن أرى أنني محبوب♪
(I've never thought that I would be loved like this.)
(لم أتوقع أبدًا أنني سأحظى بالحب بهذه الطريقة.)
Cheng Fengjie, is his mom okay?
تشنغ فينججي، هل والدته بخير؟
Jiang Shaopeng.
جيانغ شاوبنغ.
(Luckily, everything is not too late.)
(لحسن الحظ، كل شيء لم يفت الأوان بعد.)
Actually, I just have some minor wounds.
في الواقع، لدي فقط بعض الجروح البسيطة.
I'm fine.
أنا بخير.
(I haven't lost you. I can still have this.)
(لم أفقدك. لا يزال بإمكاني الحصول على هذا.)
(Zixiang: Is your mom okay?)
(زيكسيانج: هل أمك بخير؟)
Why hasn't he replied to me?
لماذا لم يرد علي؟
Whose does this jacket belong to?
لمن تعود هذه السترة؟
(It belongs to Zixiang.)
(انها تنتمي إلى زيكسيانج.)
(He forgot to take it with him that day.)
(نسي أن يأخذه معه في ذلك اليوم.)
(Just leave the chores to me.)
(فقط اترك الأعمال المنزلية لي.)
(You have just been discharged.)
(لقد تم خروجك للتو.)
It wasn't that serious.
لم يكن الأمر خطيرا إلى هذه الدرجة.
No need to be so anxious.
لا داعي للقلق .
I've washed this for you.
لقد غسلت هذا لك.
Remember to return it to him.
تذكري أن ترجعيه إليه.
Be honest with me.
كن صادقا معي.
Are you and Zixiang just normal friends?
هل أنت و زيكسيانج مجرد أصدقاء عاديين؟
(He hasn't replied.)
(لم يرد.)
The things that he said to you at the hospital
الأشياء التي قالها لك في المستشفى
made me think that you are not just normal friends.
جعلني أفكر أنكما لستما مجرد أصدقاء عاديين.
It feels like
إنه يشعر وكأنه
he cherishes you a lot.
إنه يعتز بك كثيرًا.
(I like him.)
(أنا أحبه.)
When are you going to introduce him formally to us?
متى سوف تقدمه لنا رسميًا؟
(He doesn't have a choice in his life)
(ليس لديه خيار في حياته)
(or his relationship.) [Watch on www.kisskh.la or www.kisskh.co to support Admin]
(أو علاقته.) [شاهد على www.kisskh.la أو www.kisskh.co لدعم المشرف]
(There are still some issues)
(لا تزال هناك بعض المشاكل)
(between us.)
(بيننا.)
Don't give up.
لا تستسلم.
It's not easy to find someone you like.
ليس من السهل العثور على شخص يعجبك.
It's even more precious for him
إنه أكثر قيمة بالنسبة له
to like you back.
لكي أحبك.
Tell me if you need help.
أخبرني إذا كنت بحاجة إلى مساعدة.
I'll help you knock him out and take him home.
سأساعدك على إخراجه من وعيه وإعادته إلى المنزل.
- I did the same thing to your dad too. - What are you talking about?
- لقد فعلت نفس الشيء مع والدك أيضًا. - عما تتحدث؟
What were you saying about me?
ماذا كنت تقول عني؟
(A secret.)
(سر.)
Tell me.
أخبرني.
Let's go. Come and watch some TV shows with me.
دعنا نذهب، تعال وشاهد بعض البرامج التلفزيونية معي.
Remember.
يتذكر.
Take him back to have a meal with us.
خذه لتناول وجبة معنا.
Let's go out and watch some TV shows.
دعونا نخرج لمشاهدة بعض البرامج التلفزيونية.
You let him get away.
لقد سمحته بالهروب.
You are too weak.
أنت ضعيف جدًا.
We are businessmen, not the police.
نحن رجال أعمال، وليس شرطة.
Arresting criminals is the duty of the police.
القبض على المجرمين من واجب الشرطة.
Ridiculous.
سخيف.
Young Boss has been lucky.
لقد كان الرئيس الشاب محظوظا.
Unbelievably lucky.
محظوظ بشكل لا يصدق.
He has always been like that since he was young.
لقد كان هكذا دائمًا منذ أن كان صغيرًا.
He was always fine even when everyone got hurt.
لقد كان دائمًا بخير حتى عندما أصيب الجميع بالأذى.
Luck is a type of strength too.
الحظ هو نوع من القوة أيضاً
Hey. Which is better, seen and no reply or not seen and no reply?
مرحبًا، ما هو الأفضل، المشاهدة دون رد أم عدم المشاهدة دون رد؟
Not seen and no reply is better.
لم يتم رؤيته وعدم الرد هو الأفضل.
For seen and no reply,
للمشاهدة ولا يوجد رد،
it means that I've seen it but I'm ignoring you.
يعني أنني رأيته ولكنني أتجاهلك.
For not seen and no reply, it means that I don't care at all.
لعدم الرؤية وعدم الرد، فهذا يعني أنني لا أهتم على الإطلاق.
What do you think?
ماذا تعتقد؟
What does Shaopeng
ماذا يعني شاوبنج؟
mean by this?
ماذا تقصد بهذا؟
You are cheating right in front of me.
أنت تغش أمامي مباشرة.
You are really something, Yang Zixiang.
أنت حقا شيء مميز، يانغ زيكسيانج.
Yes.
نعم.
I want to let you know
أريد أن أخبرك
how happy it is to love someone.
كم هو سعيد أن تحب أحداً.
Even if he has seen my message and hasn't replied to me, even if I'm feeling anxious,
حتى لو رأى رسالتي ولم يرد علي، حتى لو كنت أشعر بالقلق،
I'm still happy.
أنا لا أزال سعيدة.
If you can understand that,
إذا كنت تستطيع أن تفهم ذلك،
you won't treat love and marriage as disposable.
لا تتعامل مع الحب والزواج على أنهما أمران يمكن الاستغناء عنهما.
You won't use them as a tool to leave your family.
لن تستخدمهم كأداة لمغادرة عائلتك.
Both of our parents had an arranged marriage.
كان كلا والديّنا متزوجين بشكل مرتب.
It doesn't mean we have to follow in their footsteps. A marriage without love.
لا يعني هذا أن علينا أن نتبع خطاهم، فالزواج بدون حب هو الحل.
Who says there's no love?
من قال أنه لا يوجد حب؟
I like you.
أنا معجب بك.
And I like you more and more.
وأنا أحبك أكثر فأكثر.
He has replied.
لقد أجاب.
(Shaopeng: She's doing well. She wants to treat you to a meal.)
(شاوبنج: إنها بخير. تريد أن تدعوك لتناول وجبة.)
Treat this as your own home. Don't be shy.
تعامل مع هذا المكان كأنه منزلك الخاص، لا تكن خجولاً.
Yang Zixiang!
يانغ زيشيانغ!
I'm not in the mood.
أنا لست في مزاج جيد.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
He's the seventh one today.
إنه السابع اليوم.
What's going on?
ماذا يحدث هنا؟
I'm not interested.
أنا لست مهتم
Everyone has the same reactions.
كل شخص لديه نفس ردود الفعل.
It's boring.
إنه ممل.
Unlike Wang Xinjia.
على عكس وانغ شينجيا.
He's always full of surprises.
إنه دائمًا مليء بالمفاجآت.
Why is he here?
لماذا هو هنا؟
He's working here.
إنه يعمل هنا.
He can cook very well.
يمكنه الطبخ بشكل جيد للغاية.
Keep us company
ابق معنا
and I'll give you some tips.
وسأعطيك بعض النصائح.
Yes.
نعم.
Don't be shy.
لا تخجل.
I've been eyeing you for a long time.
لقد كنت أراقبك لفترة طويلة.
Let's have fun together.
دعونا نستمتع معًا.
Take a seat.
خذ مقعدا.
Here.
هنا.
Come on.
تعال.
Have a seat.
خذ مقعدا.
Let me go.
دعني أذهب.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Calm down.
اهدأ.
The server is going to hit the customer.
الخادم سوف يضرب العميل.
So fierce.
شرسة للغاية.
Who are you?
من أنت؟
You handsome man.
أنت رجل وسيم.
Let's have a drink together.
دعونا نشرب شيئا معا.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
I'm bored by myself anyway.
أنا أشعر بالملل من نفسي على أية حال.
Come.
يأتي.
Have a seat.
خذ مقعدا.
Let's drink.
دعونا نشرب.
Let's drink together.
دعونا نشرب معا.
Let's play a game.
دعونا نلعب لعبة.
The loser will drink.
الخاسر سوف يشرب
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
I'm good at it.
أنا جيد في ذلك.
You are right.
أنت محق.
You've worked hard. Be careful when you go home.
لقد عملت بجد. كن حذرًا عندما تعود إلى المنزل.
Thank you, Boss.
شكرا لك يا رئيس.
Bye.
الوداع.
Does your shift always end so late?
هل تنتهي نوبتك دائمًا في وقت متأخر؟
Are you waiting for me?
هل تنتظرني؟
I drank too much. So, I was resting.
لقد شربت كثيرًا، لذا كنت أستريح.
You left at 12:13 am.
غادرت الساعة 12:13 صباحًا.
Did you rest until now?
هل استرحت حتى الآن؟
It's 3:41 am now.
الآن الساعة 3:41 صباحًا.
You rested for more than three hours.
لقد استرحت لأكثر من ثلاث ساعات.
Why aren't you home yet?
لماذا لم تصل إلى المنزل بعد؟
Why are you so smart now?
لماذا أنت ذكي الآن؟
Just admit that you are waiting for me.
فقط اعترف بأنك تنتظرني.
Don't be so proud.
لا تكن فخوراً جداً.
You rather come out and work to earn rental money
تفضل الخروج والعمل لكسب المال من الإيجار
instead of going home?
بدلا من الذهاب إلى المنزل؟
My parents have passed away.
لقد توفي والدي.
And the house they left behind for me was taken away by my relatives.
والبيت الذي تركوه لي أخذه أقربائي.
Anyway, I'm alone.
على أية حال، أنا وحدي.
Everywhere is home for me.
كل مكان هو بمثابة موطني.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
After I've earned enough to rent a room,
بعد أن كسبت ما يكفي لاستئجار غرفة،
I'll leave.
سأرحل.
I won't take advantage of you.
لن أستغلك .
That's not what I want to talk about.
هذا ليس ما أريد التحدث عنه.
Have supper with me.
تناول العشاء معي.
I'm not hungry.
أنا لست جائعا.
You are.
أنت.
I'm not hungry!
أنا لست جائعا!
I am.
أنا أكون.
What about this?
ماذا عن هذا؟
Are you asking me?
هل تسألني؟
I think
أظن
that there are too many butterflies.
أن هناك الكثير من الفراشات.
Are you a mobile garden?
هل أنت حديقة متنقلة؟
This is too much.
هذا كثير جداً.
I think so too.
أعتقد ذلك أيضًا.
What about this?
ماذا عن هذا؟
Are you going to work as a host?
هل ستعمل كمضيف؟
How about
ماذا عن
I lend you my clothes?
هل أقرضك ملابسي؟
What about this one?
ماذا عن هذا؟
This one is not bad.
هذا ليس سيئا.
You are just going to eat at Jiang Shaopeng's house.
أنت ستذهب لتناول الطعام في منزل جيانغ شاو بينغ.
Why are you so nervous?
لماذا أنت متوترة هكذا؟
It's normal to want
من الطبيعي أن تريد
to leave a good impression in front of the person I love and his family.
ترك انطباع جيد أمام الشخص الذي أحبه وعائلته.
You'll know when you have someone you like.
ستعرف عندما يكون لديك شخص تحبه.
You just have someone you like.
لديك فقط شخص تحبه.
Why do you look so proud?
لماذا تبدو فخوراً جداً؟
Why am I thinking about him?
لماذا أفكر به؟
Could it be...
هل يمكن أن يكون...
Hi.
أهلاً.
Can I go in?
هل يمكنني الدخول؟
Welcome.
مرحباً.
Hello, Mr. Jiang.
مرحبا، السيد. جيانغ.
Honey.
عسل.
You are here.
أنت هنا.
Hello.
مرحبًا.
Congratulations on your recovery.
مبروك على شفائك.
Why are you so considerate?
لماذا أنت مهتم بهذا الأمر؟
You don't have to bring anything with you.
لا يتوجب عليك إحضار أي شيء معك.
It's the right thing to do.
هذا هو الشيء الصحيح الذي ينبغي فعله.
Mr. Jiang.
السيد جيانغ.
Come and help me out in the kitchen.
تعال وساعدني في المطبخ.
Okay.
تمام.
You can take him to the dojo.
يمكنك أن تأخذه إلى الدوجو.
Make yourself at home.
البيت بيتك.
- Make yourself at home. - Okay.
- اعتبر نفسك في المنزل. - حسنًا.
Your mom wants me to make myself at home?
هل تريد والدتك أن أجعل نفسي في المنزل؟
(She knows that I like you.)
(إنها تعلم أنني أحبك.)
Is it okay to be so open about it?
هل من المقبول أن نكون منفتحين بهذا الشأن؟
You looked so cute when you were young.
لقد كنت تبدو لطيفًا جدًا عندما كنت صغيرًا.
Do you still practice Taekwondo now?
هل لا تزال تمارس التايكوندو الآن؟
No wonder you can fight so well.
لا عجب أنك قادر على القتال بشكل جيد.
You look really...
أنت تبدو حقا...
I never thought that you would be Shuhe's colleague.
لم أكن أتوقع أبدًا أنك ستكون زميلًا لشوهي.
This must be fate.
لا بد أن يكون هذا هو القدر.
Yes.
نعم.
It must be fate.
لا بد أن يكون هذا القدر.
Let's eat.
دعونا نأكل.
Let's see if the food is to your liking.
دعونا نرى ما إذا كان الطعام يرضيك.
Thank you, Mrs. Jiang.
شكرا لك سيدة جيانغ.
Shaopeng told me that you don't eat carrots, right?
لقد أخبرني شاوبنج أنك لا تأكل الجزر، أليس كذلك؟
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Are you a kid?
هل انت طفل؟
Why are you such a picky eater at this age?
لماذا أنت من الصعب إرضائك في تناول الطعام في هذا العمر؟
Yes.
نعم.
Not only am I picky,
أنا لست انتقائيا فحسب،
but I'm also allergic to kiwis.
ولكنني أيضًا أعاني من حساسية تجاه الكيوي.
Excuse me.
اعذرني.
Hello?
مرحبًا؟
Okay.
تمام.
I'm sorry. Something happened at the company.
أنا آسف، لقد حدث شيء ما في الشركة.
I need to go back.
أحتاج إلى العودة.
So sudden?
فجأة؟
Mrs. Jiang, I'll be back tonight.
السيدة جيانغ، سأعود الليلة.
- I'll keep some food for you. - Thank you, Mrs. Jiang.
- سأحتفظ ببعض الطعام لك. - شكرا لك، سيدة جيانغ.
Go now.
إذهب الآن.
I'll get going now.
سأذهب الآن.
Be careful on the road.
كن حذرا على الطريق.
Okay.
تمام.
Let's eat.
دعونا نأكل.
Don't let the food get cold.
لا تدع الطعام يبرد.
So, this is your room.
إذن هذه غرفتك.
It feels nice.
إنه شعور جميل.
It's very heart-warming.
إنه أمر يدفئ القلب حقًا.
But it's a bit small.
لكنها صغيرة بعض الشيء.
Can I get on?
هل يمكنني الصعود؟
(What is it?)
(ما هذا؟)
It smells like you.
رائحتها تشبه رائحتك.
♪The city grooms the shadows of the two people♪
♪المدينة تعتني بظلال الشخصين♪
♪The sunset will awaken the memories♪
♪غروب الشمس سوف يوقظ الذكريات♪
♪At that moment, no names are needed♪
♪في تلك اللحظة، ليست هناك حاجة إلى أسماء♪
♪Let the world burn to dust♪
♪دع العالم يحترق إلى غبار♪
♪You are the only one who can protect me♪
♪أنت الوحيد الذي يستطيع حمايتي♪
♪We can decide on our own touching story♪
♪يمكننا أن نقرر قصتنا المؤثرة بأنفسنا♪
♪Nothing can replace this soundless love♪
لا شيء يمكن أن يحل محل هذا الحب الصامت
♪I stop talking when I see you running away from me every day♪
♪أتوقف عن الحديث عندما أراك تهرب مني كل يوم♪
♪I'm afraid to think about you, I'm losing you♪
♪أخاف أن أفكر فيك، فأنا أفقدك♪
♪I look for you from the sea of people♪
♪أبحث عنك من بين بحر الناس♪
♪I want to say I love you♪
♪أريد أن أقول أنني أحبك♪
♪I convey my love for you through the tips of our fingers♪
♪أعبر لك عن حبي من خلال أطراف أصابعنا♪
♪I can only wait like a fool because I can't hear anything♪
♪لا أستطيع إلا الانتظار مثل الأحمق لأنني لا أستطيع سماع أي شيء♪
♪I long to live in your heart♪
♪أتمنى أن أعيش في قلبك♪
♪I want to stop, I want to give up♪
♪أريد أن أتوقف، أريد أن أستسلم♪
♪I want to forget how much effort we've put into this♪
♪أريد أن أنسى مقدار الجهد الذي بذلناه في هذا الأمر♪
♪I can't forget about our promise on that day♪
♪لا أستطيع أن أنسى وعدنا في ذلك اليوم♪
♪When I close my eyes♪
♪عندما أغمض عيني♪
You like Jiang Shaopeng.
أنت تحب جيانغ شاوبنغ.
Is he why you broke your promise?
هل هو السبب في أنك خالفت وعدك؟
(The moment I see love.)
(اللحظة التي أرى فيها الحب.)
(Getting into position.) Roll the camera.
(الوصول إلى الوضع المناسب) قم بتدوير الكاميرا.
(You secretly ate again.)
(لقد أكلت سراً مرة أخرى.)
(You found out.)
(لقد اكتشفت ذلك.)
(The scenes in the script are what we do every day.)
(المشاهد الموجودة في النص هي ما نفعله كل يوم.)
(Their ears are so red.) Action!
(آذانهم حمراء جدًا.) أكشن!
Can I get on?
هل يمكنني الصعود؟